beiruting.com 2019-12-30

# Beiruting - Privacy Policy

### Information We Collect

If You choose to use Beiruting.com, we may require You to provide contact and identity information, and other personal information as indicated on the website. Once You register on the Site, You are no longer anonymous to us.

we may collect and store the following information:

Email address, physical contact information, and sometimes financial information;

Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Sites and ad data (all through cookies - You can take steps to disable cookies on Your browser, however this is likely to affect Your ability to use Sites);

Remote access codes to your server (we ask for this information if You register for a service that could not be provided without having such information);

Discussion board posts and other messages, including correspondence between us and You; and General information regarding the Beiruting.com You have registered to receive.

We do not store the following information normally:

Credit card information;

Access codes to providers of payment processing services;

Access codes to providers of domain registration services; and

Any information about your own clients.

Nevertheless we may store the information mentioned above if it is necessary for providing Service.

### Our Use of Your Information

We use Your personal information to:

provide Products and Services;

resolve disputes, calculate and collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;

verify users' identity and the information users provide;

encourage safe online experience and enforce our policies;

customize users' experience, analyze site usage, improve and measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;

communicate administrative announcements when we need to provide users with information that may affect their use of Beiruting.com;

communicate marketing and promotional offers to our users; provide customer service; and perform other business activities as described when we collect the information.

As part of your registration for Beiruting.com on the Site, You agree that You may receive certain administrative communications from us, such as administrative announcements and customer service messages regarding Beiruting.com and products during the period that we provide Beiruting.com to You, and You will not be able to opt out of receiving such administrative communications.

### Our Disclosure of Your Information

We do not sell or rent Your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without Your explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with:

service providers who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of Beiruting.com to our users.

These service providers are under confidentiality agreements with us;

law enforcement or other government officials in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of law, or as otherwise required by law.

### Notification of Changes

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on Sites. In the event of amendment, all terms shall become effective 30 days after they are initially posted to the Sites. Your continued use of Beiruting.com will constitute your acceptance of any changes or additions to this Privacy Policy.
